Dayoung Kim

Jr. Front-end Web Developer

Address

South Korea

Mobile

+82 10 2869 7886

VISA

Working Holiday Visa

Email

kimdayoung771@gmail.com

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/dayou ng-clara-kim/

Github

https://github.com/Dayoung3460

Portfolio

https://dayoungportfolio.netlify.app

EDUCATION

Youngjin programming academy
Mar 2020 ~ Sep 2020

Hotel Tourism
Deagu University
Mar 2012 ~ Feb 2017

KEY SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS / Bootstrap
- JavaScript / jQuery
- Vue.js
- React.js
- Git(Github, Gitlab)
- TypeScript
- Kotlin
- JetBrains, Webstorm

PERSONAL SUMMARY

Junior Front-End Developer experiencing in a company that develops and services a blockchain-based platform. Skilled in developing and testing multiple web-based applications. Gained skills in aligning designs with client requirements and experience in resolving conflicts with colleagues professionally. Specializes in vanilla JavaScript and vue.js framework.

WORK HISTORY

Coinvest – Gyeongsan-si, South Korea Junior Front-end web developer

: Nov 2020 ~ Present

- Collaborated with a design team to resolve CSS issues.
- Designed pages and components
- Turned design pages and components into vue.js
- Cooperated with back-end team to make API specification.
- UBIT and BES, Cryptocurrency Exchange Website (Jun 2021 ~ Present)
- Managed cryptocurrency exchange website development projects from initial design
- Used vue.js framework, Rest API(axios) and Web Socket
- Received real-time transaction data and drew a graph using Trading View chart library
- P2P exchange
- Library used:
 - grcode for OTP login
 - big-js to calculate big decimal
 - vuex
- Jangboda, a traditional market delivery application (Nov 2020 ~ May 2021)
- Developed and maintained webview for hybrid application.
- Used vue.js framework and Rest API(axios)
- Utilized Kakao map open API
- Applied NICE open API for user authentication
 - Dvue-i18n for translation
 - vue-router
 - vue-socket.io
- Recorded average 500+ monthly active users